<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>DreamTalk, AI Digital Human Integration Package for Mac</title>
    <link href="/2024/06/25/5-dreamtalk/"/>
    <url>/2024/06/25/5-dreamtalk/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="AI-Digital-Human-Integration-Package-for-Mac-DreamTalk"><a href="#AI-Digital-Human-Integration-Package-for-Mac-DreamTalk" class="headerlink" title="AI Digital Human Integration Package for Mac: DreamTalk"></a>AI Digital Human Integration Package for Mac: DreamTalk</h2><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406252239560.png"></p><p>The download link is: <a href="https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/ai-digital-human-integration-package-for-246930?u=122446863&utm_medium=clipboard_copy&utm_source=copyLink&utm_campaign=productshare_creator&utm_content=join_link">https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/ai-digital-human-integration-package-for-246930?u=122446863&utm_medium&#x3D;clipboard_copy&amp;utm_source&#x3D;copyLink&amp;utm_campaign&#x3D;productshare_creator&amp;utm_content&#x3D;join_link</a>.</p><p>DreamTalk is an audio-driven, diffusion-based emoticon pack generation framework capable of creating high-quality emoticon pack videos, covering a variety of speaking styles. DreamTalk demonstrates robust performance when processing various inputs, including songs, multilingual speech, noisy audio, and out-of-domain portraits.</p><p>DreamTalk’s signature feature is to animate a face from just a single portrait image. With the input of a voice, it’s no problem for the face to start speaking, and it can even sync lip movements and expressions to generate a video of a talking head. Based on the large model framework, DreamTalk can learn and infer expressive styles from the input voice and portrait to create personalized expression videos. Even using the same audio source, the portrait can exhibit different emotional expressions such as anger, happiness, sadness, and disdain, with corresponding facial expressions, as shown below.</p><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202403181341626.gif"></p><p>I have packaged the above tools into an easy-to-launch package, which is ready to use with a single click, avoiding various issues with downloading or configuration. </p><p><code>Please note the following computer configuration</code>:</p><ul><li>Apple Silicon M series chip</li><li><code>At least 8GB of memory</code></li></ul><h2 id="Installation-Steps"><a href="#Installation-Steps" class="headerlink" title="Installation Steps"></a>Installation Steps</h2><ol><li>Download the DMG image file from the link above.</li><li>Double-click to open the image file, and you will see the following interface:</li></ol><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406252220751.png"></p><p>   Drag the <code>app</code> file into the <code>Applications</code> folder.</p><ol start="3"><li>After copying the installation, <code>do not open it from the launchpad for the first time, right-click to open it in the Applications folder</code></li></ol><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406252221148.png"></p><ol start="4"><li>The software will automatically open the operation interface in the default browser, with the address <a href="http://127.0.0.1:7860/">http://127.0.0.1:7860/</a>, where you can start using it in the browser.</li></ol>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>AI Video Tools</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Digital Human</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>One-Click Gradio Web APP for MimicBrush on Windows</title>
    <link href="/2024/06/24/4-mimicbrush/"/>
    <url>/2024/06/24/4-mimicbrush/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="One-Click-Gradio-Web-APP-for-MimicBrush-on-Windows"><a href="#One-Click-Gradio-Web-APP-for-MimicBrush-on-Windows" class="headerlink" title="One-Click Gradio Web APP for MimicBrush on Windows"></a>One-Click Gradio Web APP for MimicBrush on Windows</h1><p>A few days ago, researchers from Alibaba, the University of Hong Kong, and Ant Group jointly launched an incredibly powerful AI tool called MimicBrush. This tool is like a “magic wand” in the realm of image editing, allowing you to easily designate areas on an image that need editing and then locally redraw them with the style of another image. Sounds cool, doesn’t it? Let’s take a closer look at just how magical this “magic wand” is!</p><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406241603671.png"></p><h2 id="Key-Features-of-MimicBrush"><a href="#Key-Features-of-MimicBrush" class="headerlink" title="Key Features of MimicBrush"></a>Key Features of MimicBrush</h2><h3 id="1-Reference-Image-Simulation"><a href="#1-Reference-Image-Simulation" class="headerlink" title="1. Reference Image Simulation"></a>1. Reference Image Simulation</h3><p>MimicBrush can analyze and replicate visual features from a reference image, then apply those features to the designated area of the source image. It’s like dressing up your picture in a new outfit, ensuring consistency in style and content.</p><h3 id="2-Zero-Sample-Image-Editing"><a href="#2-Zero-Sample-Image-Editing" class="headerlink" title="2. Zero-Sample Image Editing"></a>2. Zero-Sample Image Editing</h3><p>There’s no need for the original target image; you only need to provide a reference image containing the desired effect, and MimicBrush can achieve the editing effect via reference imitation. It’s like a “zero-entry barrier” wizard for image editing!</p><h3 id="3-Text-to-Image-Alignment"><a href="#3-Text-to-Image-Alignment" class="headerlink" title="3. Text-to-Image Alignment"></a>3. Text-to-Image Alignment</h3><p>MimicBrush also leverages a CLIP encoder and VAE to realize text-to-image alignment. You can guide the editing process by entering text descriptions, almost as if you’re telling the AI, “Do it this way!”</p><h3 id="4-Diversified-Editing-Results"><a href="#4-Diversified-Editing-Results" class="headerlink" title="4. Diversified Editing Results"></a>4. Diversified Editing Results</h3><p>Whether it’s local area editing, texture transfer, or post-processing optimization, MimicBrush can showcase a variety of editing results, freeing your creativity from the limitations of tools.</p><h2 id="Application-Scenarios"><a href="#Application-Scenarios" class="headerlink" title="Application Scenarios"></a>Application Scenarios</h2><p>MimicBrush is particularly suitable for product customization, character design, and special effects production. It not only simplifies complex editing workflows but also greatly enhances editing efficiency and flexibility. Its underlying framework is based on the combination of the SD1.5 diffusion model and the MimicBrush model, making it the “ultimate weapon” in AI image editing.</p><h2 id="Quick-Start-Guide"><a href="#Quick-Start-Guide" class="headerlink" title="Quick Start Guide"></a>Quick Start Guide</h2><p>MimicBrush has been packaged into a one-click launch bundle, which you can use with a simple click, eliminating worries about configuration issues. </p><p>Download URL: <a href="https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/one-click-gradio-web-app-for-mimicbrush-245730?u=122446863&utm_medium=clipboard_copy&utm_source=copyLink&utm_campaign=productshare_creator&utm_content=join_link">https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/one-click-gradio-web-app-for-mimicbrush-245730?u=122446863&utm_medium&#x3D;clipboard_copy&amp;utm_source&#x3D;copyLink&amp;utm_campaign&#x3D;productshare_creator&amp;utm_content&#x3D;join_link</a></p><h3 id="System-Requirements"><a href="#System-Requirements" class="headerlink" title="System Requirements"></a>System Requirements</h3><ul><li>Windows 10&#x2F;11 64-bit OS</li><li>NVIDIA graphics card with 8GB VRAM or more</li></ul><h3 id="Download-and-Tutorial"><a href="#Download-and-Tutorial" class="headerlink" title="Download and Tutorial"></a>Download and Tutorial</h3><ol><li><strong>Download the Zip File</strong> and <strong>Unzip the File</strong>:</li></ol><p>After unzipping, avoid having Chinese characters in the path. Double-click the “run.exe” file to run, as shown below.</p><p> <img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406242141596.png"></p><ol start="2"><li><strong>Access via Browser</strong>:</li></ol><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406241543218.png"></p><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406241543672.png"></p><p>Open your browser and visit <a href="http://127.0.0.1:7860/">http://127.0.0.1:7860/</a> to use MimicBrush in the browser.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>AI Image Tools</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Windows</tag>
      
      <tag>Image Editing</tag>
      
      <tag>Image Generator</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Standalone Facefusion 2.6.1 for Windows</title>
    <link href="/2024/06/23/3-AI%20%E6%8D%A2%E8%84%B8%20Facefusion%20windows/"/>
    <url>/2024/06/23/3-AI%20%E6%8D%A2%E8%84%B8%20Facefusion%20windows/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Standalone Facefusion 2.6.1: An AI Face Swapping Application for Windows</p><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406232128515.png"></p><p>Facefusion is an open-source AI tool for video&#x2F;image face swapping. It features a brand-new user interface and offers a web-based operation similar to Stable Diffusion, significantly enhancing the user experience. The fusion capability of this tool can accurately integrate the facial features of the target into a template image, creating a new image with the target’s facial traits while maintaining the original posture, expression, and actions. Facefusion supports various fusion modes, including single-face fusion, multi-face fusion, and specific facial feature fusion.</p><h2 id="Installation-Guide"><a href="#Installation-Guide" class="headerlink" title="Installation Guide"></a>Installation Guide</h2><p>Facefusion 2.6.1 has been packaged into a one-click launcher, allowing immediate use and avoiding various issues that can occur during environment setup.</p><p><code>Please ensure your computer meets the following specifications</code>:</p><ul><li>Windows 10&#x2F;11 64-bit operating system</li><li>NVIDIA graphics card or CPU operation</li></ul><p>standalone application download URL: <a href="https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/standalone-facefusion-2-6-1-ai-face-for-243457?u=122446863&utm_medium=clipboard_copy&utm_source=copyLink&utm_campaign=productshare_creator&utm_content=join_link">https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/standalone-facefusion-2-6-1-ai-face-for-243457?u=122446863&utm_medium&#x3D;clipboard_copy&amp;utm_source&#x3D;copyLink&amp;utm_campaign&#x3D;productshare_creator&amp;utm_content&#x3D;join_link</a></p><h2 id="Download-and-Usage-Tutorial"><a href="#Download-and-Usage-Tutorial" class="headerlink" title="Download and Usage Tutorial"></a>Download and Usage Tutorial</h2><ul><li>After downloading the zip file, unzip it and double-click the <code>run.exe</code> file to run it. CUDA and Python environments are already built-in.</li></ul><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406221750197.png"></p><ul><li>Use a browser to access <a href="http://127.0.0.1:7860/">http://127.0.0.1:7860/</a>, and you can use it directly in the browser.</li></ul><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406221755637.png"></p><p>Dear friends, if you find this article helpful, please give it a thumbs up 👍</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>AI Image Tools</category>
      
      <category>AI Video Tools</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Face Swap</tag>
      
      <tag>Image Face Swap</tag>
      
      <tag>Video Face Swap</tag>
      
      <tag>Windows</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Mac Exclusive Large Model Standalone Application Chat-with-MLX, Supporting RAG！</title>
    <link href="/2024/06/23/2-chatwithmlx/"/>
    <url>/2024/06/23/2-chatwithmlx/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Mac-Exclusive-Large-Model-Standalone-Application-Chat-with-MLX-Supporting-RAG！"><a href="#Mac-Exclusive-Large-Model-Standalone-Application-Chat-with-MLX-Supporting-RAG！" class="headerlink" title="Mac Exclusive Large Model Standalone Application Chat-with-MLX, Supporting RAG！"></a>Mac Exclusive Large Model Standalone Application Chat-with-MLX, Supporting RAG！</h1><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406221201790.jpeg"></p><p>Hello everyone, today I want to introduce a revolutionary product designed specifically for Apple Silicon Macs—[<strong>Chat with MLX</strong>]:<a href="https://github.com/qnguyen3/chat-with-mlx">https://github.com/qnguyen3/chat-with-mlx</a>! </p><p>This is not just a chat tool but a full-featured large language model chat interface. It leverages Apple’s MLX framework to provide an unprecedented level of privacy protection and chat experience. Chat with MLX is based on Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) technology, capable of interacting with various open-source models, supporting multiple file formats, and adding YouTube videos via URL. This application supports multilingual interaction, easily integrates any HuggingFace and MLX-compatible open-source models, and is particularly suitable for use on macOS and Apple Silicon.</p><h2 id="Highlights-of-Chat-with-MLX"><a href="#Highlights-of-Chat-with-MLX" class="headerlink" title="Highlights of Chat-with-MLX"></a>Highlights of Chat-with-MLX</h2><p><strong>Chat-with-MLX</strong> is a chat interface based on “Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)” that can utilize multiple open-source models to enhance the chat experience. With this tool, users can interact with their data, supporting various file formats (such as doc(x), pdf, txt) and adding YouTube videos via URL. It supports multilingual interaction, including English, Spanish, Chinese, Vietnamese, and Turkish. Additionally, Chat-with-MLX can easily integrate any HuggingFace and MLX-compatible open-source models, providing a native RAG example for macOS and Apple Silicon.</p><h3 id="Use-Cases"><a href="#Use-Cases" class="headerlink" title="Use Cases"></a>Use Cases</h3><ol><li><strong>Multilingual Data Query</strong>: When you need to query specific data in different languages, whether it’s text, PDF files, or online videos.</li><li><strong>Enhance Chat Experience with Powerful Models</strong>: Utilize advanced open-source models (such as Google Gemma, Mistral, StableLM, etc.) to improve the responsiveness and accuracy of chat applications.</li><li><strong>Research and Development</strong>: Ideal for users with research and development needs in AI and machine learning, especially in an Apple Silicon (e.g., M1 chip) environment, leveraging the MLX framework for efficient development and testing.</li><li><strong>Document Management and Retrieval</strong>: When you need to retrieve information from a large amount of text or multimedia content, providing a more intuitive and faster access method.</li></ol><h3 id="Key-Features"><a href="#Key-Features" class="headerlink" title="Key Features"></a>Key Features</h3><ul><li><strong>Supports chatting with data</strong>, including various file formats and YouTube videos.</li><li><strong>Multilingual support</strong>.</li><li><strong>Easily integrates various HuggingFace and MLX-compatible open-source models</strong>.</li><li><strong>Native RAG support on macOS and Apple Silicon</strong>.</li></ul><h2 id="Installation-Guide"><a href="#Installation-Guide" class="headerlink" title="Installation Guide"></a>Installation Guide</h2><p>To simplify the installation process, Chat-with-MLX is packaged into a standalone launcher. Users can run it with a simple click, without the need to configure a complex Python environment.</p><p>Chat with MLX  standalone application download URL: <a href="https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/chat-with-mlx-standalone-application-for-243328?u=122446863&utm_medium=clipboard_copy&utm_source=copyLink&utm_campaign=productshare_creator&utm_content=join_link">https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/chat-with-mlx-standalone-application-for-243328?u=122446863&utm_medium&#x3D;clipboard_copy&amp;utm_source&#x3D;copyLink&amp;utm_campaign&#x3D;productshare_creator&amp;utm_content&#x3D;join_link</a></p><p><strong>Note: The Chat-with-MLX App only supports devices equipped with the Mac M1&#x2F;2&#x2F;3 series chips.</strong></p><h3 id="Installation-Steps"><a href="#Installation-Steps" class="headerlink" title="Installation Steps"></a>Installation Steps</h3><ol><li>Download the DMG image file from the above link, and drag the <code>app</code> file into the <code>Applications</code> folder.</li><li>After the installation is complete, <strong>do not open it from the Launchpad for the first time; instead, right-click to open it in the Applications folder</strong>, as shown below. For more details, refer to <a href="https://aifun.fans/58">Common Issues with Installing Software on Mac</a>.</li><li>The software will automatically open the operation interface in the default browser, with the address <a href="http://127.0.0.1:7860/">http://127.0.0.1:7860/</a>. You can start using it in the browser at this point.</li></ol><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406221149917.png" alt="Interface Preview"></p><ul><li>After selecting a model, click to load the model to start chatting. Click on RAG settings to load local data.</li></ul><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406221150989.png" alt="Model Selection"></p><ul><li>In addition to the integrated Tongyi Qianwen model, you can also add other MLX models in the model management section.</li></ul><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406221150594.png" alt="Model Management"></p><h3 id="Model-and-Memory-Configuration"><a href="#Model-and-Memory-Configuration" class="headerlink" title="Model and Memory Configuration"></a>Model and Memory Configuration</h3><p>The table below shows the availability of different model sizes under various memory configurations. The left value in each cell indicates the availability of 4-bit quantization, while the right value indicates the availability of 8-bit quantization for the corresponding model size and memory combination.</p><p>For example, if your model size is between 14B and 34B parameters and you have 48GB of memory, you can use 4-bit quantization (✅), but 8-bit quantization is not available (❌).</p><table><thead><tr><th align="center">Model Size&#x2F;Memory</th><th align="center">0.5B ~ 4B</th><th align="center">6B ~ 13B</th><th align="center">14B ~ 34B</th><th align="center">40B ~ 56B</th><th align="center">65B ~ 72B</th><th align="center">100B ~ 180B</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td align="center">8GB</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td></tr><tr><td align="center">18GB</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td></tr><tr><td align="center">36GB</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td></tr><tr><td align="center">48GB</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td></tr><tr><td align="center">64GB</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">❌&#x2F;❌</td></tr><tr><td align="center">96GB</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td></tr><tr><td align="center">192GB</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;✅</td><td align="center">✅&#x2F;❌</td></tr></tbody></table><p>Dear friends, if you find this article helpful, please give it a thumbs up 👍 ! Let’s enjoy the new AI chat experience on Mac together!</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>AI Text Generators</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>MLX</tag>
      
      <tag>Chat-with-MLX</tag>
      
      <tag>LLMs</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Portable Facefusion 2.6.1 for Mac with Apple silicon</title>
    <link href="/2024/06/23/1-AI%20%E6%8D%A2%E8%84%B8%20Facefusion%20%E7%8B%AC%E5%AE%B6%20Mac%20%E7%89%88App/"/>
    <url>/2024/06/23/1-AI%20%E6%8D%A2%E8%84%B8%20Facefusion%20%E7%8B%AC%E5%AE%B6%20Mac%20%E7%89%88App/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Facefusion-AI-Face-Swap-App-for-Mac"><a href="#Facefusion-AI-Face-Swap-App-for-Mac" class="headerlink" title="Facefusion: AI Face Swap App for Mac"></a>Facefusion: AI Face Swap App for Mac</h1><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406212024476.png"></p><p>Facefusion is an open-source AI video&#x2F;picture face swapping tool. It comes with a brand new user interface and offers a web page operation similar to Stable Diffusion, greatly enhancing the user experience. The face fusion feature of this tool can precisely infuse the characteristics of the target face into the template image, generating a new image that contains the target facial features while maintaining the original posture, expression, and movement. Facefusion supports various fusion modes, including single face fusion, multi-face fusion, and specific face selection fusion.</p><h2 id="Installation-Guide"><a href="#Installation-Guide" class="headerlink" title="Installation Guide"></a>Installation Guide</h2><p>To simplify the installation process, Facefusion is packaged into a standalone launcher. Users can run it with a simple click, without the need to configure a complex Python environment.</p><p><strong>Note: The Facefusion App only supports devices equipped with the Mac M1&#x2F;2&#x2F;3 series chips.</strong></p><p>Download URL：<a href="https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/portable-facefusion-2-6-1-for-mac-with-185633?u=122446863&utm_medium=clipboard_copy&utm_source=copyLink&utm_campaign=productshare_creator&utm_content=join_link">https://www.patreon.com/user/shop/portable-facefusion-2-6-1-for-mac-with-185633?u=122446863&utm_medium&#x3D;clipboard_copy&amp;utm_source&#x3D;copyLink&amp;utm_campaign&#x3D;productshare_creator&amp;utm_content&#x3D;join_link</a></p><h3 id="Installation-Steps"><a href="#Installation-Steps" class="headerlink" title="Installation Steps"></a>Installation Steps</h3><ol><li>Download the DMG image file from the link above.</li><li>Double-click to open the image file, and you will see the following interface:</li></ol><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406212025875.png"></p><p>   Drag the <code>app</code> file into the <code>Applications</code> folder.</p><ol start="3"><li><p>In the <code>Applications</code> folder, find the app, right-click and choose “Open” to avoid security restrictions on the first launch.  </p></li><li><p>The first launch may take some time, please be patient. </p></li><li><p>The software will automatically open the operation interface in the default browser, the address is <a href="http://127.0.0.1:7860/">http://127.0.0.1:7860/</a>, and now you can start using Facefusion in the browser.</p></li></ol><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406212025926.png"></p><h3 id="Usage-Suggestions"><a href="#Usage-Suggestions" class="headerlink" title="Usage Suggestions"></a>Usage Suggestions</h3><ul><li><p>The AI face swap model of Facefusion is pre-installed locally, so it can be used normally without an internet connection.</p></li><li><p>To improve running speed, it is recommended to select the <code>coreml</code> option during use.</p></li></ul><p><img src="https://cdn.xueshu.fun/202406212150019.png"></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>AI Image Tools</category>
      
      <category>AI Video Tools</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Face Swap</tag>
      
      <tag>Image Face Swap</tag>
      
      <tag>Video Face Swap</tag>
      
      <tag>Mac</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
